marvell.com 2014-11-21

# Marvell - Legal - Privacy Statement

## Use of the Marvell Internet Site Privacy Statement

Marvell is committed to respecting your privacy. You can visit Marvell on the Web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Once you choose to provide us personally identifiable information, you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with Marvell.

This statement regarding the privacy of the personally identifiable information you provide online covers five main areas: Awareness, Choice, Access, Security, and Oversight.

### AWARENESS

Marvell provides this Online Privacy Statement to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at the bottom of every marvell.com page.

**What we collect**

If you browse Marvell's Web site anonymously, we don't collect personal information. Otherwise, we may collect your contact and company information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which parts of our Web site you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable.

**How we use it**

Marvell uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, and to personalize our Web sites for you.

**Who we share it with**

Marvell will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other Marvell entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such Marvell entities and/or business partners, including those in the United States and/or any other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements.

### ACCESS

Links to third party Web sites on the site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave this site. Marvell has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their Privacy Policy. Thus, Marvell does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this site, you do this entirely at your own risk.

### SECURITY

Marvell is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### OVERSIGHT

If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send us a message through our feedback form.

### MARVELL'S PRIVACY POLICY

Marvell Semiconductor, Inc.'s privacy policy is subject to change at any time and without notice. Please check here for updates.

Copyright © 2005. Marvell International Ltd. All rights reserved. Marvell, the Marvell logo, Moving Forward Faster, Alaska, Fastwriter, GalNet, PHYAdvantage and Prestera are registered trademarks of Marvell. Discovery, DSP Switcher, GalTis, Horizon, Libertas, Link Street, NetGX, RADLAN, Raising The Technology Bar, The Technology Within, UniMAC, Virtual Cable Tester, and Yukon are trademarks of Marvell. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.

Marvell comprises Marvell Technology Group Ltd. and its subsidiaries, Marvell International Ltd. (MIL), Marvell Semiconductor, Inc. (MSI), Marvell Asia Pte. Ltd. (MAPL), Marvell Japan K.K. (MJKK), Marvell Semiconductor Israel Ltd. (MSIL), RADLAN Computer Communications Ltd., and SysKonnect GmbH.
